Guide to the Julian C. Smith papers, 1900-2015.
Smith, Julian C. papers
- Series II. Correspondence
  - Professional Correspondence
    - Prof. K. Stephen - Institut fur Technische Thermodynamik und Tehrmische Verfahrenstechnik, 1977-09-09-1977-10-06 (Box 9, Folder 84)
    - Kenneth S. Canfield, 1977-09-19-1978-02-27 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Enrico Sismondo, 1977-10-20 (Box 9, Folder 86)
    - John V. Vance, 1977-10-28-1977-11-02 (Box 9, Folder 93)
    - William B. Corydon, 1977-12-05-1978-04-18 (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Dr. J. B. Helme, 1978-01-22-1978-11-26 (Box 9, Folder 55)
    - Joslyn A. Smith, 1978-02-05-1978-02-14 (Box 9, Folder 82)
    - Patrick H. McNamara, 1978-07-1979-02-02 (Box 9, Folder 65)
    - Sr. R. R. Kraybill, 1978-09-20 (Box 9, Folder 59)
    - M. D. Morris, 1978-10-02-1981-09-17 (Box 9, Folder 67)
    - Clifton C. Sutton, 1978-10-18 (Box 9, Folder 87)
    - Vincent W. Uhl, 1978-11-30 (Box 9, Folder 92)
    - Peter C. Green, 1979-01-13-1979-01-18 (Box 9, Folder 52)
    - Seminars, 1979-04-03-1980-02-18 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Chemical Engineering Education, 1979-04-06-1981-11 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Samuel W. Bodman, 1979-04-26 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Ken Zinn, 1979-05-21 (Box 9, Folder 98)
    - N.Y.S. Science & Technology Foundation, 1979-06-06-1982-06-15 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Walter C. Gates, 1979-08-06-1979-08-31 (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - Hugh L. Myers, 1980-01-09 (Box 9, Folder 68)
    - Ralph T. Reeve, 1980-01-28 (Box 9, Folder 78)
    - Norman MacLeod, 1980-04-15-1982-08-03 (Box 9, Folder 63)
    - Dr. B. N. Srimani, 1980-06-17-1980-07-02 (Box 9, Folder 88)
    - National Science Foundation Review, 1980-08-20-1980-09-05 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - U. S. Hattiangadi, 1980-10 (Box 9, Folder 54)
    - Dr. E. Cranch - Worcester Polytechnic Institute, 1981-01-14 (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Council for Chemical Research, 1981-04-24 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - William B. Weaver III, 1981-06-18-1982-06-21 (Box 9, Folder 95)
    - Robert H. Herrmann, 1981-08-10-1981-09-01 (Box 9, Folder 56)
    - Charles B. Thompson, 1981-08-20 (Box 9, Folder 90)
    - Prof. Charles ReVelle - John Hopkins University, 1981-10-09-1981-11-04 (Box 9, Folder 79)
    - George Ward, 1981-10-10-1981-11-23 (Box 9, Folder 94)
    - Gerald C. Rappe, 1981-11-25 (Box 9, Folder 76)
    - E. Firth Perryman, 1982-01-11-1982-01-18 (Box 9, Folder 73)
    - Irwin B. Margiloff, 1982-02-05 (Box 9, Folder 66)
    - John Rudel, 1982-02-11-1982-02-23 (Box 9, Folder 80)
    - Dr. William J. Nicholson, 1982-03-17-1983-03-28 (Box 9, Folder 71)
    - John E. Powers, 1982-03-18-1982-05-20 (Box 9, Folder 74)
    - John B. Carberry, 1982-04-22-1982-05-05 (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Jim Latimore, 1982-05-21-1982-06-02 (Box 9, Folder 61)
    - Robert H. McBride, 1982-06-01-1982-06-21 (Box 9, Folder 64)
    - Dan Rathmann, 1982-06-01-1982-09-08 (Box 9, Folder 77)
    - Proctor & Gamble Visit, 1982-08-11-1982-10-14 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Dwight F. Ryan - Xerox Corporation, 1982-08-16-1982-08-30 (Box 9, Folder 81)
    - A. M. Bernard, 1982-11-15-1982-11-30 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Steven R. Wilson, 1982-12-12-1982-12-17 (Box 9, Folder 96)
    - Derjiun LeeReference Letters, 1984-07-16-1985-01-09 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Kenneth Ackley File, 1985-01-23-1987-05-23 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      Includes correspondence, agendas
    - Solvay-White ILR, 1985-07-30-1985-09-17 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Ray Yang Reference Letters, 1988-1994-08 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - AIChE Warren K. Lewis Award & Related Materials, 2008-07-28-2008-11-19 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Series III. Publications & Related Materials
  - Engineering Related
    - Unit Operations 7th Ed. Annotated Manuscript - Chapters 23-29, undated (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - References Notes - Unit Operations, undated (Box 18)
    - Elements of Processing Equipment Book Scope, Philosophy, Plan, Outlines, undated (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Technical Publications, 1941-1986-05; Smith Jr., Julian Cleveland (Box 18)
    - Article Reprints, 1941-05-1941-09 (Box 14, Folder 33)
      Includes articles
    - Mixed Article Reprints, 1942-02-1948-08 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Published Articles, 1944-01-1966 (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - Centrifuge Article Reprints, 1947-04-1955-09 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Prepublication Correspondence, Data, etc., 1947-10-16-1949-01-04 (Box 14, Folder 30)
      Includes correspondence, articles
    - Technical Publications - General, 1948-05-27-1976-03-16 (Box 14, Folder 34)
      Includes correspondence, notes
    - Nitrobenzene & Other Article Reprints, 1949-10-1951-01 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - The Rise of Engineering Research at Cornell, 1950-1985-09-23 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      Correspondence from August 1985 to September 1985
    - The Rise of Engineering Research at Cornell - Data, 1950-1985 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Mixed Article Reprints, 1950-06-1951-09 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Glass Article Reprints, 1951-04-1962-08-08 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Proceedings of the Conference on Soil Stabilization, 1952-06-18-1952-06-20 (Box 10)
      Held at Massachusetts Institute of Technology, includes article by J. C. Smith "The Chrome-Lignin Process and Ion Exchange Studies" & discussion of "Incorporation of Admixtures with Soil" by V. H. Rodes
    - Trends in Heat Exchange Article, 1953-06 (Box 14, Folder 26)
      Includes article
    - Centrifuge Article, 1953-08-27-1956-01-12 (Box 14, Folder 24)
      Includes correspondence, drafts
    - Flow of Solids in Bulk Handling Systems, 1954-03; University of Utah (Box 10)
      Vol. 45 No. 9, Bulletin No. 64
      Salt Lake City, Utah
    - Article on Methyl Amines, 1954-07-13-1955-04-28 (Box 14, Folder 25)
      Includes draft, notes, correspondence, charts
    - Book "X" Notes, 1955-1959-11 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Perry Handbook - Centrifuges, 1955-06-01-1967-11-17 (Box 14, Folder 4)
      Includes correspondence, draft of contribution, notes, articles
    - On the Theory of Plastic Flow of Coulomb Solids, 1958-05; University of Utah (Box 10)
      Vol. 49 No. 16, Bulletin No. 91
    - Shape Factors, 1958-09 (Box 14, Folder 23)
      Includes articles, note
    - Perry Handbook 4th Edition, 1959-1961 (Box 14, Folder 3)
      Includes notes, drafts
    - Perry Handbook 4th Edition - Section 19 Final Edited Manuscript, 1959-1961 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Parameter Article, 1959-04-09-1964-10-02 (Box 14, Folder 14)
      Includes correspondence, notes, papers
    - Perry Handbook 4th Edition - Separator Selection, 1959-12-11-1962-11-10 (Box 14, Folder 5)
      Includes correspondence, draft of contribution
    - IEC Paper - Applications of Centrifuges, 1959-12-11-1965-11-02 (Box 14, Folder 21)
      Includes correspondence, articles, photos, notes
    - Costs of Centrifuges II, 1960-06-03-1960-12-05 (Box 14, Folder 22)
      Includes article, correspondence
    - Profiling Solids Flow from Bins, 1960-08-08-1985-12-23 (Box 10, Folder 11)
      Correspondence from May 1976 to December 1985
    - Parameter Article, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Pulsation Article, 1961-09-28-1968-11-06 (Box 14, Folder 17)
      Includes correspondence, articles, draft, notes
    - Godleski Paper, 1961-11-15-1970-04-09 (Box 14, Folder 18)
      Includes correspondence, notes, articles, drafts
    - Article on HF Diagram, 1962-04-20-1966-10-13 (Box 14, Folder 15)
      Includes correspondence, notes, drafts
    - Baasel Article, 1962-04-26-1965-10-01 (Box 14, Folder 16)
      Includes correspondence, article, draft
    - Article on Radiant Heater, 1962-05-01-1962-10-04 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Mixing in Fluidized Beds - Nicholson Paper, 1964-04-02-1971-06-30 (Box 14, Folder 13)
      Includes notes, drafts, correspondence
    - AIChE paper on 5 year program, 1966-09-1967-08-23 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Perry Handbook 5th Edition, 1969-04-15-1973-12-20 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Professional Graduate Programs Article, 1971-1972 (Box 14, Folder 11)
      Includes notes, draft
    - Applications of Drying Technology, 1973-04-05 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - AIChE Energy Panel, 1975-05-1976-10-07 (Box 10, Folder 19)
      Includes articles, correspondence, bulletins
    - Selection and Testing of Process Equipment Book Notes, 1976-11-18-1977-03-23 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Chemical Industry in Malaysia and Nigeria, 1977-09-1981-12-08 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Mixing Article - Chilton, 1977-12-02-1978-01-04 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Evaluation of Chemical Industry in Developing Countries, 1978-10-17-1980-09-05 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Encyclopedia of Science & Technology: Centrifugation, 1979-12-21-1983-11-10 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Perry Handbook 6th Edition, 1980-08-26-1984-11-13 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Chemical Engineering at Cornell University, 1984-08-03-1985 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - The School of Chemical Engineering at Cornell: A History of the First Fifty Years, 1988; Smith Jr., Julian Cleveland; Cornell University College of Engineering (Box 18)
      Cornell Engineering Histories Vol. 1, 2 copies - one signed
    - Suggestions - Unit Operations 6th Ed., 1988-05-17-2009-08-15 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Engineering: Cornell Quarterly, 1988-06-1989-11; Cornell University College of Engineering (Box 18)
      Vol. 22 No. 4, Vol. 24 No. 1
    - Continuing Engineering Education - 1965-71, 1990-12-10-1991-04-15 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Unit Operations of Chemical Engineering, 2001; McCabe, Warren L.; Smith, Julian C.; Harriott, Peter; McGraw-Hill (Box 18)
      6th Edition; Revised annotated copy
    - Unit Operations 7th Ed. Notes, 2002-10-21-2004-11-09 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Preface, About the Authors, Index - Unit Operations 7th Ed., 2003-2004 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Peter Harriott Notes - Unit Operations 7th Ed., 2003-2004 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Edited Copy - Unit Operations 7th Ed., 2004-06-10-2004-09-14 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Unit Operations of Chemical Engineering, 2005; McCabe, Warren L.; Smith, Julian C.; Harriott, Peter; McGraw-Hill (Box 18)
      7th Edition; Signed by Julian C. Smith & Peter Harriott
    - AIChE Annual Meeting Program Book, 2008-11-16-2008-11-21; American Institute of Chemical Engineers (Box 18)
      Philadelphia, Pennsylvania
    - Olin Hall News, 2013-10; Cornell School of Chemical and Biomolecular Engineering (Box 18)
      No. 103
  - Other
    - Cornell in Pictures: 1868-1954, 1954; Young, Charles V. P.; Cornell University Press (Box 18)
      Includes Class of '41 60th Reunion photo taken June 8, 2001
    - Cornell Alumni News, 1984-07 (Box 18)
    - Breaking Ninety: A History of the Country Club of Ithaca 1900-1989, 1990; Smith Jr., Julian Cleveland (Box 18)
    - Cornell University 138th Commencement Program, 2006-05-28; Cornell University (Box 18)
    - Acacia Fraternity at Cornell: The First Century, 2007; Balcerski, Thomas J. (Box 18)
    - Memories and Beyond, 2008; ChemE's Class of 1953 (Box 18)
    - The Alpha Delta Phi 180th Anniversary Ed. Catalogue, 2012; Alpha Delta Phi Fraternity (Box 18)
      Morton Grove, Illinois
  - Reviews
    - Reviewing, 1952-11-23-1991-09-03 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - McGraw-Hill Continuing Education Reviews, 1965-10-29-1968-03-21 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Reviewing, 1987-10-30 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Series IV. Teaching & Cornell University
  - Departmental
    - Fred "Dusty" H. Rhodes Dinner, 1956-01-04-1957-10-28 (Box 4, Folder 54)
      Includes correspondence, program, speech, biography packet
    - University Faculty Meeting Minutes, 1963-05-13-1964-05-27 (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Events of 1969, 1969-04-21-1981-03 (Box 4, Folder 55)
      Includes materials on Willard Straight Hall takeover, University government, Vietnam War, President Perkins' resignation
    - Coal Preparation for Conversion Conference, 1974-1975-08 (Box 9, Folder 102)
    - Laser Induced Chemistry Applications, 1974-12-18-1980-10-08 (Box 9, Folder 103)
    - Decision Days, 1975-10-1977-11 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Cornell Society of Women Engineers, 1976-01-26-1981-02-02 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Seminar Speakers, 1976-08-02-1978-10-25 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Science, Technology & Society Program, 1976-09-1981-04 (Box 9, Folder 6)
      Includes correspondence, various publications
    - Community College Days, 1976-10-1977-11 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Engineering Student Ambassadors, 1977-01-19 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - National Society of Black Engineers, 1977-04-15-1982-06-11 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Freshman Open House, 1977-05-1982-02 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - ITV Program, 1977-08-29-1979-01-12 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Fred H. T. Rhodes Inauguration, 1977-09-23-1977-11-29 (Box 4, Folder 48)
      Includes program, schedule, participant information
    - Design & Project Management Fluid Bed Boilers, 1977-11-30 (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Minority Engineering Visitation, 1978-04-19-1982-04-05 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Science, Technology & Society AID Workshop, 1979-07-06-1979-12-04 (Box 9, Folder 7)
      Includes bulletin, notes, schedules, reports
    - Center for International Studies, 1979-09-25-1980-01-21 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Dreyfus Distinguished Lecture Series, 1980-12-18-1981-05-01 (Box 9, Folder 101)
    - Minority Introduction to Engineering (MITE) Program, 1981-08-06-1983-06-24 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Navy DASO Visit, 1982-01 (Box 9, Folder 100)
      Includes correspondence, itinerary, visit packet
    - Julian C. Smith Testimonial Dinner, 1983-09-19-1983-11-09 (Box 4, Folder 49)
      Includes correspondence, guest list, speech
    - Julian C. Smith Dinner, 1983-10-1987-05-21 (Box 4, Folder 53)
      Includes correspondence, cards, invitations, programs, articles
    - United Way Campaign - College of Engineering, 1985-10-29-1986-01-15 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Graduate Program
    - Student Advisees
      - Dwarkanath Akerkar, 1960-1967-08-25 (Box 11, Folder 1)
      - William Baasel, 1958-09-05-1962-05-09 (Box 11, Folder 2)
      - Eva Barta, 1958-10-06-1960-02-27 (Box 11, Folder 3)
      - Martin Cantor, 1957-11-25-1958-07-23 (Box 11, Folder 4)
      - George H. Forsberg, 1963-08-28-1964-07-01 (Box 11, Folder 5)
      - Howard L. Greene, 1960-05-12-1960-06-27 (Box 11, Folder 6)
      - Edward Godleski, 1960-02-16-1961-05-31 (Box 11, Folder 7)
      - Halsey Griswold, 1951-10-22-1954-04-30 (Box 11, Folder 8)
      - Uday S. Hattiangadi, 1964-03-18-1975-09-04 (Box 11, Folder 9)
      - William Henkel, 1962-02-10-1966-05 (Box 11, Folder 10)
      - John Hull, 1955-06-28-1957-02-27 (Box 11, Folder 11)
      - John L. Johnson, 1958-10-02-1959-06-08 (Box 11, Folder 12)
      - Ashok Joshi & Alfred Francis, 1949-08-16-1965-04-16 (Box 11, Folder 13)
      - Charles Krutchen, 1961-08-29-1962-05 (Box 11, Folder 14)
      - Richard Knittel, 1960-10-03-1962-03 (Box 11, Folder 15)
      - Lloyd Kusak, 1953-09-1963-03-18 (Box 11, Folder 16)
      - Marshall Lipman, 1954-09-1956-03-19 (Box 11, Folder 17)
      - Walter Maier, 1963-02-06-1966-07-01 (Box 11, Folder 18)
      - Wilford Mathewson, 1959-05-25-1963-01-11 (Box 11, Folder 19)
      - William Nicholson, 1963-06-17-1965 (Box 11, Folder 20)
      - Hai Nguyen, 1971-03-1974-08-16 (Box 11, Folder 21)
      - Constantine Polidoroff, 1971-0-4-05-1979-03-24 (Box 11, Folder 22)
      - Robert B. Samworth, 1963-09-1966-04-21 (Box 11, Folder 23)
      - David Schubert, 1950-10-06-1950-09-02 (Box 11, Folder 24)
      - Leroy Sinclair, 1965-04-13-1966-08-08 (Box 11, Folder 25)
      - Gerald Talandis, 1960-05-18-1961-05-16 (Box 11, Folder 26)
      - Jesse Tarleton, 1953-06-13-1958-05-30 (Box 11, Folder 27)
      - Edward Unger, 1941-04-1955-12-06 (Box 11, Folder 28)
      - Clay Wagner, 1952-03-03-1954-02-05 (Box 11, Folder 29)
      - Ronald M. Yarbroff, 1961-02-13-1965-08-05 (Box 11, Folder 30)
      - Carle Zimmerman, 1960-09-1962-10 (Box 11, Folder 31)
      - Master of Engineering, 1984-01-20-1985-10-29 (Box 11, Folder 32)
      - Academic Advising, 1978-08-1979-02 (Box 11, Folder 36)
      - Sophomore Advising, 1977-10-13-1978-10-04 (Box 11, Folder 37)
      - Master of Engineering Advising, 1973-08-08-1978-05-24 (Box 11, Folder 38)
      - Advising, 1973-02-05-1981-08-20 (Box 11, Folder 46)
      - C. Anzueto, 1984-06-09-1984-09-14 (Box 11, Folder 47)
      - Carolyn Bender, 1983-02-15-1983-08-31 (Box 11, Folder 48)
      - Winston Jenks, 1983-02-15-1984-05 (Box 11, Folder 49)
      - Katherine Krause, 1982-02-03-1983-07-11 (Box 11, Folder 50)
      - David Lai, 1983-02-22-1983-08-31 (Box 11, Folder 51)
      - Michael Marinovic, 1983-02-15-1984-05 (Box 11, Folder 52)
      - Junga Panikamparambil, 1983-02-22-1983-09-20 (Box 11, Folder 53)
      - John Rinko, 1983-02-15-1984-02-02 (Box 11, Folder 54)
      - Ignacio Schmidt, 1983-02-22-1983-09-19 (Box 11, Folder 55)
      - Mark Seliger, 1983-02-15-1983-09-22 (Box 11, Folder 56)
      - Joseph Wroblicka, 1983-02-15-1984-01-26 (Box 11, Folder 57)
      - James Zuegel, 1983-02-15-1984-05 (Box 11, Folder 58)
    - Design Project
      - M. Eng Project - D. Busch & J. Sharkness, 1971-12-1975-01-13 (Box 11, Folder 44)
      - M. Eng Project - S. Tilak, V. Arora & K. Khan, 1973-09-1974-12 (Box 11, Folder 45)
      - M. Eng Project, 1975-06-1976-03 (Box 11, Folder 43)
      - Moltox Plant M. Eng Project, 1983-10-13-1984-06-01 (Box 11, Folder 42)
      - M. Eng Project, 1983-10-25-1984-01-04 (Box 11, Folder 41)
      - Air Products M. Eng Project, 1984-01-17-1986-05-21 (Box 11, Folder 39)
      - MeOH Air Products M. Eng Project, 1985-02-01-1985-06-14 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Co-op Program
    - Co-op Program, 1969-07-29-1979-11-19 (Box 11, Folder 64)
    - Co-op Program, 1977-04-07-1978-04-25 (Box 11, Folder 61)
    - Co-op Program - Companies, 1977-08-15-1981-12-21 (Box 11, Folder 63)
    - Co-op Program, 1979-04-30-1981-04-02 (Box 11, Folder 60)
    - Co-op Program, 1980-01-25-1980-08 (Box 11, Folder 62)
    - Co-op Program, 1980-12-01-1983-01-25 (Box 11, Folder 59)
  - Heat Transfer Course
    - Solution Notes, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      Includes notes
    - ChE 5506 - 1970 - Visual Cards, 1970-1974-11-21 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      Includes transparencies, problem sets, handwritten notes, articles
  - Equipment Courses
    - ChE 563: Process Equipment Design & Selection
      - ChE 563 - Flow Meters, undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
        Includes transparencies, bulletins, catalogs
      - Plate Columns, Stacked Columns, 1961-09-1977-08 (Box 2, Folder 22)
        Includes articles, transparencies, correspondence
      - ChE 563 - Blowers and Compressors, 1968-1977-10-11 (Box 2, Folder 10)
        Includes transparencies, articles, bulletins, correspondence
      - ChE 563 - Heat Exchanger, 1968-04-08-1984-07 (Box 2, Folder 9)
        Includes articles, transparencies, bulletins, project assignment, correspondence
      - ChE 563 - Solid Mixers, 1969-03-1980-11 (Box 2, Folder 6)
        Includes transparencies, articles
      - ChE 563 - Leaching & Extraction, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - ChE 563 - Paste & Rubber Mixers, 1973-1983-08-23 (Box 2, Folder 3)
        Includes transparencies, correspondence, photos, articles
      - ChE 563 - Reference Articles, 1973-11-1981-08 (Box 2, Folder 18)
        Includes articles, bulletin
      - ChE 563 - Motionless Mixers, 1973-12-07-1980-05-27 (Box 2, Folder 5)
        Includes transparencies, correspondence, photos, articles, order forms
      - Process Design Course - General; Codes, 1974-05-20-1985-12 (Box 2, Folder 12)
        Includes problem sets, course evaluations, syllabus, catalog, exams, correspondence, articles
      - ChE 563 - Condensers, Heat Pipes, 1976-01-1985-08 (Box 2, Folder 24)
        Includes articles, transparencies, correspondence, bulletins
      - Pipe, Valves, Seals, 1976-09-1983-08 (Box 2, Folder 13)
        Includes transparencies, bulletins, articles, problem sets
      - ChE 563 - Absorbers, Gas Cleaning Equipment, 1977-08-29-1979-09 (Box 2, Folder 19)
        Includes transparencies, bulletins, article
      - ChE 563 - Storage Vessels, 1978-11-14-1983-08 (Box 2, Folder 15)
        Includes equation sheet, transparencies, catalog, articles
      - ChE 563 - Notes 1981-1982, 1979-1983 (Box 2, Folder 16)
        Includes exams, handouts, syllabus, problem sets, handwritten notes
      - ChE 563 - Pumps, 1983-08-23-1985 (Box 2, Folder 17)
        Includes transparencies, bulletins, articles
    - ChE 5625
      - 5625 - Size Reduction, 1952-05-1973-11 (Box 2, Folder 21)
        Includes transparencies, symposium leaflets, bulletins, articles
      - 5625 - Dryers, 1962-06-1977-06 (Box 2, Folder 27)
        Includes transparencies, bulletins, correspondence, articles
      - 5625 - Filters, 1966-03-28-1983-02-02 (Box 2, Folder 25)
        Includes correspondence, transparencies, articles, bulletins
      - 5625 - Glass-lined Equipment, General Pictures, 1972-1976-03 (Box 2, Folder 20)
        Includes bulletins
      - 5625 - Sedimenters, 1977-1984-01-30 (Box 2, Folder 26)
        Includes transparencies, handouts, articles
    - ChE 5609
      - 5609 - Material, 1957-01-1969-11 (Box 2, Folder 28)
        Includes transparencies, problem sets, article, bulletin, quiz, correspondence
      - 5609 - Zlokarnik References, 1969-09-1973-09 (Box 2, Folder 29)
        Includes correspondence, notes, exams, bulletins, problem sets, transparencies, articles
  - Other Courses
    - Unknown
      - Furnaces, Radiant Heaters, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
        Includes transparencies
      - James R. Katzer Seminar, undated (Box 11, Folder 66)
      - Two-Phase Flow, 1959-01-12-1979 (Box 2, Folder 11)
        Includes transparencies, articles, bulletins
      - 4th Year Design, 1964-03-1973-04 (Box 11, Folder 65)
      - Boilers, Vaporizers, 1965-05-1979-12 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      - Screens; Dry Separators, 1965-10-25-1980 (Box 2, Folder 23)
        Includes articles, bulletins
      - Master of Engineering Design: HF Plant, 1978-02-14 (Box 11, Folder 35)
      - Master of Engineering Design, 1979-02 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - ChE 421: Organic Chemical Course
      - ChE 421 - Vinyl Chloride, undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
        Includes bulletin
      - ChE 421 - Penicillin, undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
        Includes transparencies, homework, bulletin
      - ChE 421 - Substitute Natural Gas (SNG), undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
      - ChE 421 - Styrene, undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
        Includes bulletin, transparencies, notes
      - ChE 421 - Chloromethanes & Ethyl Bromide, undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
      - ChE 421 - Citric Acid, undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
        Includes transparencies, notes
      - ChE 421 - Ethanol & Methanol, undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
      - ChE 421 - Methyl Parathion, undated (Box 4, Folder 56)
      - ChE 421 - Sec-Butyl Alcohol, undated (Box 4, Folder 24)
        Includes transparency
      - ChE 421, undated (Box 4, Folder 31)
      - ChE 421 - Methylamines (DMA), 1948-1978 (Box 4, Folder 15)
        Includes homework, transparencies, notes, articles
      - ChE 421 - Beet Sugar, 1963-08 (Box 4, Folder 59)
        Includes transparencies, notes, photographs
      - ChE 421, 1973-02-1983-05 (Box 4, Folder 27)
        Includes notes, transparencies, articles
      - ChE 421 - Petroleum Processes, 1974-08 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - ChE 421 - Organic Processes, 1974-08-1980-04 (Box 4, Folder 26)
        Includes papers, notes, transparencies
      - ChE 421 - Glycol, 1975-03-1979-01 (Box 4, Folder 19)
        Includes transparencies, notes, articles
      - ChE 421 - Phenol, 1976-03 (Box 4, Folder 9)
      - ChE 421 - Hexamethylenetetramine, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 20)
      - ChE 421 - Acetic Anhydride, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 57)
      - ChE 421 - Nitroglycerin (NG), 1977-02-1980-02 (Box 4, Folder 3)
        Includes articles, transparencies, diagrams
      - ChE 421 - Student Talks, 1977-02-1981 (Box 4, Folder 25)
        Includes assignment, schedule, notes
      - ChE 421 - Fermentation Processes, 1978-04 (Box 4, Folder 17)
        Includes lecture notes, transparencies